Guide to the Women's Studies Program records, 1981-2008 (bulk 1981-2002) UA.25.41.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Programs/Events, 1981-2001; 2
  - Nancy Ziegenmeyer, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Anita Hill, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Named speaker funds, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Jane Schulenberg, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Patricia Derian (Harland fund), 1992 (Box 11)
  - "The sporting woman" exhibit, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Women and sports exhibit catalog, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Marguerite de Navarre Colloquium (Harland fund), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Joan Ringelheim (Harland fund), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Dissertation seminars, 1992-1995 (Box 11)
  - Programs, 1992-1993; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Take back the byte, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Violence against women conference, 1993 (Box 11)
  - 10th Anniversary planning: General, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series program/brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Budget/arrangements, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Chandra Mohanty, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Kristine Stiles, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Mandy Merck, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Kathy Ferguson, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Amy Richlin, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary lecture series: Deborah Gray White, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Cynthia Enloe, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Sara Evans, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Karla Holloway, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Michael Kimmel, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Barbara Ogur, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Naomi Wolf, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Nan Keohane, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Performances, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Program, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Publicity, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Articles, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Books, 1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary photographs, 1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Catering, Hotel, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: Participants, discussion leaders, 1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary symposium: "Power breakfast" with Nan Keohane, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary events: Conversations on a journey (book publication), 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary events: Talking gender production, 1995-1998 (Box 12)
  - 10th anniversary events: Anthology, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Programs (planning), 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Departmental speaker awards, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Departmental speaker awards, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Bev Hitchens workshop: Speaking comfortably in public, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Women musicians in Venice: Jane Baldauf: Berdes archive, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Ad-hoc speaker cosponsorships: Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Graduate workshops, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Raleigh Fine Arts Society: Mary Metz, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Women's leadership project, ad-hoc speakers, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - The feminist majority expo, Washington DC, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Elizabeth Kennedy, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Women, violence, and the arts of survival, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Departmental speaker awards, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Departmental speaker awards: Sponsorship requests turned down, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Programs sponsored, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Graduate workshop, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Feminist colloquium, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Feminist colloquium: Mary Katzenstein, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Feminist colloquium: Nelly McKay, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Locating feminism lecture series: advance planning, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Locating feminism lecture series: Publicity, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Locating feminism lecture series: Introductions, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Locating feminism lecture series: Abstracts, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Locating feminism lecture series: Proceedings, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Feminist Colloquium/Colloquium on global feminism: Charlotte Bunch, Tani Barlow, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Feminist Colloquium/Colloquium on global feminism: Tani Barlow, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Programs (cosponsored), 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - 2001 symposium, 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - 2001 symposium, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Workshop on conference presenting/moderating, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Programs (cosponsored), 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Program, 1999; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Participants, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Steering committee minutes, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Call for papers, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Keynote speaker, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Community partners, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Corporate sponsors, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Hotel and other arrangements, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 24/7 rest and unrest conference: Tabloid, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Celebration dinner for Jean Fox O'Barr, 2001 (Box 13)
- Scholarships/Awards, 1984-2000; 3
  The Scholarships and Awards series of the Women's Studies Program records includes materials related to scholarships and awards given to undergraduate and graduate students as well as faculty and scholars. Included are materials related to the funding and formation of named scholarship funds such as the Annie McDougal Memorial Award, the Dora Ann Little Award, and the Anne Firor Scott Research Award, scholarship awards for students; Mainstreaming Grants, awards given to Duke faculty to develop and teach classes in their own areas of specialty that included women and women's roles and accomplishments in transformative ways; and other awards. Materials include correspondence, announcements, budgets, award guidelines, curriculur materials, and others.
  - Mary Faison Alden service-learning award, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Awards and winners, 1997-1999 (Box 13)
  - Distinguished alumni award: Dottie Simpson, 1997-1999 (Box 13)
  - Distinguished alumni award: Margaret Taylor Smith, 1993-1996 (Box 13)
  - Fellows proposal and set-up, 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Fellows work and schedule, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Fellows program, 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Ernestine Friedl research award, 1997-1999 (Box 14)
  - Gender and race award, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Graduate student funding memo and descriptions, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Lee-Ewig graduate fellowship, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Dora Anne Little award, 1990-1999 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Fish, Tepaske, Monsman, Lawrence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Winston, Ewald, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Lewis and Clark, Lochmuller, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1987 (Box 24)
    Personnel restriction until 2057.
  - Mainstreaming grants: Partin, Wharton, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Documentation, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Summer research awards: All materials, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Robisheaux, Solterer, Undated (Box 14)
  - Formulative Evaluation Research Association (FERA) study, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming grants: Mailing, 1989; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming and faculty research grants, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming and faculty research grants, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Mainstreaming award, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Summer research grant, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Anne McDougall Memorial award, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Anne McDougall award: Publicity, Announcements, Invitations, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Anne McDougall award: Committee and letters to/from applicants, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Anne McDougall award, 1985-1998 (Box 14)
  - Anne Firor Scott research award, 1990-1997 (Box 14)
- Annual Report, 1983-2002; 4
  The Annual Reports series of the Women's Studies Program records consists of drafts and copies of the annual reports put together by the Women's Studies Program director and administrators. The report compiled accomplishments, events and activities, press coverage, scholarship, and milestones and was distributed to University administrators and others. Included in this series are correspondence, newsclippings, notes, draft reports, event flyers and information, and other materials.
  - Women's studies annual report, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Annual report, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Annual report, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Historical material, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Annual reports, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 1997-1998 (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 1998-2001 (Box 15)
  - Annual report, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Annual report: Cathy Davidson's talk, 2002 (Box 15)
- Council on Women's Studies, 1985-2004; 5
  The Council on Women's Studies series of the Women's Studies Program records includes materials related to the formation, operation, and activities of the Council. The bulk of the series is related to the meetings and events planned and hosted by the Council, which included both academic programming as well as networking and fundraising activities. Also included are materials related to the creation, structure, membership, and committees of the Council, and copies of the Friends of Women's Studies Newsletter distributed by the Council.
  - General and Administrative, 1985-2002; 5.1
    The General and Administrative subseries of the Council on Women's Studies series includes materials related to the formation, structure, operations, and membership of the Council. Included are correspondence, minutes, bylaws, directories, memorandums, and committee materials, among others. Topics include the selection of new members for the Council, Council member responsibilities, Council activities, and other subjects.
    - Council set-up documents, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
    - Operating plan review and campaign reports, 1985-1992 (Box 15)
    - Bylaws, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Council budget and timeline, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - Memos/mailings to council members, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
    - Memos/correspondence with council, 1986-2001 (Box 15)
    - Council minutes, 1986-2003 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1986-1988 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1988-1990 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1990-1992 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1992-1994 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1994-1997 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 2000-2002 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 1998-2001 (Box 15)
    - Nominating committee, 2002-2004 (Box 15)
    - Anlyan, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
    - Directory, 1988-1992 (Box 15)
    - Directory, 1993-1995 (Box 15)
    - Directory, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Directory, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Directory, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Directory, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Directory, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Packet for new council member orientation, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Mentorship program ideas, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Honorary members, 1989, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Fact sheets for council, 1989-2001 (Box 16)
    - Trustee nominations, 1992 (Box 24)
      Board of Trustees restriction until 2042.
    - Nominations, 1992-2002 (Box 16)
    - Women's studies timeline, 1995-1998 (Box 16)
    - Council document, 1996 (Box 16)
    - End-of-year tax deduction letter, 1996, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Council surveys, 1996 (Box 16)
    - Council correspondence, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Council RSVPs, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Council on women's studies handout, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Alumni/development calendar, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Sister mentors, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Student members of council, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Council fact sheet, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Council mailing, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Council bylaws, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Council diversity committee, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Director's council letter, 2002 (Box 16)
    - External affairs committee, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Council committees, 2003 (Box 16)
    - March 17 conference call, 2003 (Box 16)
    - March 20 conference call: Joanne, Robyn, Pat, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Meetings and Retreats, 1986-2004; 5.2
    The Meetings and Retreats subseries of the Council on Women's Studies series includes materials related to the major activities of the Council, the two large meetings or retreats held each year for attendees with some interest in the Women's Studies Program. Meetings typically lasted two or more days and included speakers and programs for attendees as well as business meetings for the Council; while one meeting per year was held in Durham, the second large meeting for the year was usually held in other cities with large populations of Duke women graduates. Meeting themes and content were often structured as academic or professional conferences focusing on a theme related to Women's Studies. Retreats were for members of the Council but typically included programming open to the public. Included are planning materials, budgets, invitation and attendee lists, correspondence, logistical information, agendas, minutes, articles and readings, and other materials.
    - February 27-28, 1986 Council Meeting, Jan-Mar 1986 (Box 16)
    - Council meeting packet, Feb 1986 (Box 16)
    - February council meeting report, Feb-Mar 1986 (Box 16)
    - February council meeting follow up letters, Feb-Jun 1986 (Box 16)
    - Fall 1986 council meeting packet, Jul-Oct 1986 (Box 16)
    - April 3-4, 1987 council meeting: Arrangements, material, invites, Dec 1986-Apr 1987; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - April 3-4 council meeting: Responses, Apr-Jul 1987 (Box 16)
    - Symposium tapes, April 04 1987 (Box 25, Audio-cassette UA25410001-CS-0001, Audio-cassette UA25410001-CS-0002)
    - Fall 1987 council meeting (Box 16)
    - April 1988 council meeting, Jan-May 1988 (Box 16)
    - October 2-3 council meeting: Dialogues, Aug-Nov 1988 (Box 16)
    - October 2-3 council meeting: Everything else, Aug-Nov 1988 (Box 16)
    - March 5, 1989 council meeting, October 1988-March 1989 (Box 16)
    - March 5, 1989 council meeting: Follow up letters, Mar-May 1989 (Box 16)
    - October 21-22, 1989 council meeting (Box 16)
    - October 22, 1989 council business meeting: Agenda, attachments, minutes, Sep-Nov 1989 (Box 17)
    - March 24-25, 1990 council meeting, Dec 1989-Mar 1990 (Box 17)
    - March 24-25, 1990 council meeting: Invitations, Feb-Apr 1990 (Box 17)
    - October 13-14, 1990 council meeting Atlanta, Aug-Nov 1990 (Box 17)
    - Rethinking Women's History: Dr. Kristen Neushel, October 13 1990 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA25410001-VHS-0003)
    - Personal Perspectives on Women's Studies, October 13 1990 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA25410001-VHS-0004)
    - Fall 1992 council meeting: New York (Box 17)
    - April 1991 council meeting, Mar-Jun 1991 (Box 17)
    - Fall 1991 council meeting: Washington, D.C., Apr-Aug 1991 (Box 17)
    - April 11-12 council meeting, 1992 (Box 17)
    - New York prospects/invites, 1992 (Box 17)
    - May 8-9, 1993 council meeting, Jan-May 1993 (Box 17)
    - October 9, 1993 council meeting, Oct 1993 (Box 17)
    - Chicago program: Friends of women's studies gathering, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Chicago budget, communications, and handouts, 1993 (Box 17)
    - March 20, 1994 council meeting, Jan-Mar 1994 (Box 17)
    - October 30, 1994 council business meeting, Oct 1994 (Box 17)
    - Washington D.C. friends of women's studies meeting, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Washington D.C. friends meeting: Participants, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Washington D.C. friends meeting: Budget, communications, and handouts, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Spring 1995 council meeting, Jan-Mar 1995 (Box 17)
    - Fall 1995 council meeting, Apr-Nov 1995 (Box 17)
    - Atlanta friends meeting, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Atlanta friends meeting: Participants, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Atlanta friends meeting: Budget and publicity, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Spring 1996 council business meeting, Apr-May 1996 (Box 17)
    - Spring 1996 council meeting, Sep 1995-Apr 1996 (Box 17)
    - Fall 1996 council agenda/business meeting, Oct 1996 (Box 17)
    - Charlotte friends of women's studies meeting: Invitations, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Charlotte friends meeting: Planning/committee, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Charlotte friends meeting: Budget/speakers, 1996 (Box 17)
    - March 14-16, 1997 council retreat, Nov 1996-Mar 1997 (Box 17)
    - March 14-16, 1997 council retreat: Articles and handouts, Mar 1997 (Box 17)
    - November 1997 council business meeting, Sep-Nov 1997 (Box 17)
    - Boston friends of women's studies meeting: Planning, committee and arrangements, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Boston friends meeting: Budget, brochure/publicity and speakers, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Boston friends meeting: Participants, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Mar 6-8, 1998 council agenda, Dec 1997-Mar 1998 (Box 17)
    - Margaret Taylor Smith Celebration, Mar 6-8, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Mar 6-8, 1998 hotels, meals, etc., Feb-Mar 1998 (Box 18)
    - Nov 15 business meeting, Nov 1998 (Box 18)
    - Dallas friends of women's studies meeting: Speakers/program and planning, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Dallas friends meeting: Budget, brochure, and arrangements, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Dallas friends meeting: Participants, 1998 (Box 18)
    - May 23, 1999 business meeting, May 1999 (Box 18)
    - Council on WS retreat, Feb-May 1999 (Box 18)
    - Retreat follow-up, May 1999-May 2000 (Box 18)
    - October 3, 1999 business meeting, Oct 1999 (Box 18)
    - Business meeting New York City, May 2000 (Box 18)
    - New York City friends of women's studies meeting: Program, 2000 (Box 18)
    - New York City friends meeting: Packets and evaluations, 2000 (Box 18)
    - New York City friends meeting: Sponsors/Budget, Publicity/Brochure and Arrangements, 2000 (Box 18)
    - New York City friends meeting: Planning committee and council, 1998-2000 (Box 18)
    - New York City friends meeting: Duke magazine article, photos, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Nov 2000 council on WS retreat, aqueduct conference center, Aug-Nov 2000 (Box 18)
    - Nov 12, 2000 business meeting, aqueduct, Oct-Nov 2000 (Box 18)
    - Mar 25, 2001 business meeting, Washington, D.C., Feb-May 2001 (Box 18)
    - Washington, D.C. friends of women's studies: Program, council planners/involvement, and council participants, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Washington, D.C. friends meeting: Ellen Goodman, Ph.D. workshop and conference materials, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Washington, D.C. friends meeting: Registration lists, invites, evaluations, and follow-ups, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Washington, D.C. friends meeting: Tribute plans and memory quilt by council members, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Council on Women's Studies retreat, Aqueduct conference center: Business meeting, Nov 2001 (Box 18)
    - Council on Women's Studies retreat, Aqueduct conference center: Business meeting notes, November 2001 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Council retreat: Arrangements, Sep-Nov 2001 (Box 18)
    - Retreat courses/participants, Apr-Nov 2001 (Box 18)
    - Council retreat RSVPs, Oct 2001 (Box 18)
    - April 2002 council meeting: Princeton, Apr 2002 (Box 18)
    - Sep 14, 2002 meeting packet (Box 18)
    - Sep 13-14 meeting notes, Sep 2002 (Box 18)
    - New York City council event, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Feb 9, 2003 council meeting, Jan-Feb 2003 (Box 18)
    - Feb 9, 2003 business meeting, Feb 2003 (Box 18)
    - May 31, 2003 executive committee meeting, May 2003 (Box 18)
    - Restructuring executive business meeting, Oct 2002-May 2003 (Box 18)
    - Spring 2004 council retreat, 2003-2004 (Box 18)
      Administrative restriction until 2029
  - Other Events, 1986-2002; 5.3
    The Other Events subseries of the Council on Women's Studies series includes materials related to events planned or hosted by the Council aside from the large semi-annual multi-day meetings described in the previous subseries. The events included in this series are typically receptions or informal meals (lunches, dinners, or teas) held in different cities for members of the Council on Women's Studies and Women's Studies Program administrators to meet and network with alumni and other women for donations or other involvement with the program. Included are correspondence, planning documents, invitation lists, and other materials.
    - Atlanta, 1987-1995 (Box 19)
    - Atlanta seminar: T Boatwright, 1994 (Box 19)
    - Atlanta, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - Baltimore, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Boston, 1992, 1996 (Box 19)
    - California (Santa Barbra), 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - Charlotte, 1994-1996, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Charlotte, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Charlottesville, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Chicago, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - Colorado (Denver and Colorado Springs, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Connecticut (New Haven) and Westchester Co., NY, 2001-2002 (Box 19)
    - Dallas, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - Durham, NC events, 1986-1987 (Box 19)
    - Florida (Tampa and Orlando), 2001 (Box 19)
    - Greensboro, 1988-1989, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Ithaka, 2000 (Box 19)
    - New Jersey, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - New Mexico (Santa Fe and Albuquerque), 2000 (Box 19)
    - New Orleans, 2000, 2002 (Box 19)
    - New York City, 1986-2002 (Box 19)
    - New York, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - Philadelphia, Undated (Box 19)
    - Portland, OR, 2002 (Box 19)
    - San Francisco: Jenkins, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
    - Seattle, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Tulsa, OK, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Washington, D.C., 1988-1989 (Box 19)
    - Washington, D.C., 1990 (Box 19)
    - Washington, D.C. women's forum, 1996-1998 (Box 19)
    - Washington, D.C. young alums reception, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Washington, D.C., 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - Cookie's coffees, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Eleanor (musical), 1999 (Box 19)
    - Event rosters, 1991-2001 (Box 19)
    - Friends of women's studies events, 1989-1997 (Box 19)
    - Carolyn Heilbrum tea, May 1999 (Box 19)
    - Reunion weekends, 1997, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Gala reunion weekends, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - Gala reunion weekend, 2001-2002 (Box 19)
  - Friends Newsletter, 1988-1992; 5.4
    The Friends of Women's Studies Newsletter series includes a complete run of the newsletter published by the Council on Women's Studies for alumni and friends of the Women's Studies Program from 1988 through 1992, as well as some materials related to the compiling, editing, and publishing of the newsletter.
    - Targeted mailing of 2400 brochures, Apr 1990 (Box 19)
    - Spring 1988 newsletter (Box 19)
    - Fall 1988 newsletter (Box 19)
    - Spring 1989 newsletter (Box 19)
    - Fall 1989 newsletter (Box 19)
    - FN5, 1990 (Box 19)
    - FN6, 1990 (Box 19)
    - FN7, 1990 (Box 19)
    - FN8, 1991 (Box 19)
    - FN9 Spring 1991 (Box 19)
    - FN10 Fall 1991 (Box 19)
    - FN11 Winter newsletter, 1992 (Box 19)
    - FN12 Spring 1992 (Box 19)
- Survey, 1987-1988; 6